Thank you for watching!
I'm going to do my best.
Is this okay?
I'm not doing anything.
I want to take a picture of this.
What is this?
I'm scared.
Is it a crane?
Which team is it?
Tell me.
Where is Ichi?
Ichi is there.
Wait.
What are you dancing?
I don't know.
Hide your eyes.
I'm scared.
Can I make a pig nose?
Please.
This is dangerous.
This is a formation.
Be careful.
Why?
Don't touch my butt.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
What?
Miu.
I'm going to do it.
Do something.
Did you notice?
Is this right?
I'm scared.
Are you ready?
Don't think about anything.
Listen to me.
Aim for the pig nose.
I'm scared.
This is a stage.
Kyo Expression.
What?
I'm coming!
What was the choreography?
What was that?
I'm coming!
Jihan are you ready?
Yes I'm ready.
It's rare that Hiroyuki, Tak Fate, and
Takamatsu here practices together.
Small talk
I'm going to start.
Ready, go!
What is it?
I'm going to start.
Oh!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm sorry.
This is more than I thought.
Wow.
It was better than I thought.
I thought it was going to be a good
one.
I didn't know what I was doing.
It was a good one.
I'm sorry.
I think the result is good.
I think so, too.
It's the first time.
I'm going to practice blindfolded from
now on.
Blindfolded?
It's a new scene.
It was difficult.
I'm going to practice blindfolded.
I think so, too.
We're going to practice blindfolded.
I don't think so.
I'm going to practice blindfolded.
Shuffle doesn't matter what you say.
What is the first title of the song?
Riki Oshida's
How about the flower?
Everyone is different.
How about the song of the second half?
Not good at drinking
That's it!
Cute.
I'll do it.
What about you?
You're definitely a human.
I'll eat it.
I'm definitely a human.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
OK.
Music start!
Wow!
Dance!
Yeah!
Everyone, let's have fun!
It's fast!
Move forward a little.
Music start!
Wow!
Ha! Ha!
It's hard.
I can't do this.
Ha! Ha!
Music start!
Wow!
Music stop!
Thank you for watching!
What's next?
Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm so good.
They can still go through the dance!
Way to go!
Moving on to the last move!
ometer has been manipulated for a
mistake
The rap is back to normal.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Georgina defends耶
Shiny is jumping
phrasing
It's just a reaction
Jump!
Butong Genki
frizz
She is good
I'm chasing you.
I've come to you like a child.
You're like a PC.
I miss you.
I'm not good at this.
I can't do it.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
I'm a party people.
What song is that?
That's返事.
What did you do!!!
I'm on a diet!
I'm done!
Saiko is on a diet.
You can do it with your neck.
I can do it with my neck.
Karin!
I think I was in the same group as you.
Eili!
I'm going to do it.
You're a break dancer.
I'm going to do it with my body.
I think it's good.
That's great.
Do you want to do it with your body?
I'm going to do it with my body.
Help me!
I'm not moving at all.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I want to do this kind of project
again.
Maybe we can play different songs at
the concert.
I want to show you how much we can do.
I know.
I'm not moving at all.
Please watch our next video.
Thank you for watching.
That's all!
We are IZINAMI's stylist, IZINAMI's
costume, GANSTA!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
Push the like button!